Ji Su Park

Neuroscience graduate

Driven Neuroscience graduate with extensive laboratory research as well as entrepreneurial and consulting experience. Analytical and detailoriented team player with broad background in science and visual art. Complementary skills in programming, UX/UI design and product planning. With my combined expertise, I'm passionate to develop inclusive and comprehensive healthcare services in the future.

isp02014@gmail.com

+82 010-7171-0777



Boramero 5-gil 43 Borame Samsung Chereville #4706, Seoul, South Korea

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Neuroscience with Minor in Visual Arts

Sep 2014 - May 2018

Johns Hopkins University

Baltimore, Maryland

Relevant course work

- Introduction to Programming, Probability and Statistics, Nervous System, Intro to Cognitive Neuropsychology
- Digital Photography, Painting Workshop II, Studio Drawing, Photo and Text

Brent International School Manila

Sep 2010 - May 2014

Manila, Philippines

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Strategy Manager

DoAl Inc.

Feb 2021 - Mar 2021

A Medical AI company that develops digital healthcare services

Achievements/Tasks

- · Worked as a business strategy manager and handled market research for several products including DoPap Smear and DoKaryotpe.
- Planned, researched, designed a new version of IR presentation for KOTRA Startup oversea expansion application.

Assistant Manager

Exogen Pte. Ltd.

Nov 2019 - May 2020

A Singapore based consulting company focused on oversea expansion of biotech companies

Achievements/Tasks

- · Worked on Singapore expansion of biomarker based breast cancer screening product for a company.
- Planned, directed and produced sales/marketing materials for Singaporean consumers and medical professionals.
- · Prepared presentations for overseas expansion for countries such as Saudi Arabia, China, Singapore, Brazil and others.

Research Analyst

A.T. Kearney

Sep - Oct 2019

A consulting company

Achievements/Tasks

• Worked as a research analyst for a conglomerate on Digital Transformation strategy project.

Research Intern

Kantar Healthcare

Aug-Sep 2019

A Market Research company

Achievements/Tasks

· Worked as an intern to review/gather data and to translate interviews for market research project on arthritis biologics medicine.

Research Assistant

The Sung-Yon Kim Laboratory

A neuroscience lab at Seoul National University

Achievements/Tasks

Expansion Microscopy (Optical microscopy technique)

- Worked on developing new method for expansion microcopy.
- Utilized a confocal microscope to image Thy-1 mouse brain tissues, C. elegans and human samples before and after expansion.

Homeostasis on Mouse Model (Optogenetics)

- Performed s stereotaxic surgery on mouse such as virus injection and fiber photometry implants.
- Performed behavioral experiments using optogenetics to discover relationships between homeostasis and various brain regions such as lateral parabrachial nucleus and lateral hypothalamus.

Contact: Sung-Yon Kim, Associate Professor of Chemistry sungyonkim@snu.ac.kr

Research Assistant

The Seth Blackshaw Laboratory

Dec 2017 - May 2018

Oct 2018 - May 2019

A neuroscience lab at Johns Hopkins Medical Campus

Achievements/Tasks

- · Worked with Dr. Fatemeh Rajaii on researching the orbital fat cell differentiation and hormonal effect in mice and human
- Investigated Thyroid associated orbitopathy (TAO) using mouse model

Contact: Fatemeh Rajaii, Assistant Professor of Ophthalmology Wilmer Eye Institute frajaii1@jhmi.edu

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCES

Joo-Young Jeong Entrepreneurship Competition

May 2020

Project leader, UI/UX designer

Designed a pet supply information search and recommendation app service.

IBM Call for Code Hackathon

Jun 12 - 13, 2020

Project leader, Front-end coder, UI/UX designer

Team "Forthebetter" - Designed and developed a prototype app for block-chain based donation app service.

Shinhan Bank Service(product) Designer Bootcamp

Jul - Aug 2020

Product designer, UI/UX designer

Designed and developed a pet obesity management app service through extensive user research.

OTHER EXPERIENCE

42Seoul "La Piscine" Programming Bootcamp

Mar 2021 - Apr 2021

Studied C languages intensively through 42Ecole's coursework and system. Learned Linux commands and functions of C language and algorithms including dfs.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Python, MATLAB, JavaScript (React Native), HTML, CSS, C

Design Tools Adobe XD, Photoshop, Lightroom, Illustrator, InDesign, 3ds Max, Zbrush

Microsoft Office Proficient in Word, Excel and highly experienced in PowerPoint

PUBLICATIONS

Wiley Online Library Advanced Science

Sep 30, 2019

Scalable and Isotropic Expansion of Tissues with Simply Tunable Expansion Ratio

Authors

Han-Eol Park¹, Dongkil Choi¹, **Ji Su Park**, Changgon Sim, Sohyun Park, Sunah Kang, Hyunsoo Lim, Myungsun Lee, Jaeyoun Kim, Jinyoung Pac, Kunsoo Rhee, Junho Lee, Yunjong Lee, Yan Lee* and Sung-Yon Kim*